<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>寻寻觅觅</title>
  
  
  <link href="/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="http://yoursite.com/"/>
  <updated>2019-01-18T03:38:59.208Z</updated>
  <id>http://yoursite.com/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>寻寻觅觅</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="http://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>测试文章</title>
    <link href="http://yoursite.com/2019/01/14/first-bolgs/"/>
    <id>http://yoursite.com/2019/01/14/first-bolgs/</id>
    <published>2019-01-13T16:00:00.000Z</published>
    <updated>2019-01-18T03:38:59.208Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<pre><code>前言：本文是一篇测试文章，截取自马丁路德金的《I have a Dream》。</code></pre><a id="more"></a><h1 id="测试标题1"><a href="#测试标题1" class="headerlink" title="测试标题1"></a>测试标题1</h1><p>Five score years ago, a great American, in whose symbolic shadow we stand<br>today, signed the Emancipation Proclamation. This momentous decree came as a<br>great beacon light of hope to millions of Negro slaves who had been seared in<br>the flames of withering injustice. It came as a joyous daybreak to end the<br>long night of their captivity.</p><h1 id="测试标题2"><a href="#测试标题2" class="headerlink" title="测试标题2"></a>测试标题2</h1><p>But one hundred years later, the Negro still is not free. One hundred years<br>later, the life of the Negro is still sadly crippled by the manacles of<br>segregation and the chains of discrimination. One hundred years later, the<br>Negro lives on a lonely island of poverty in the midst of a vast ocean of<br>material prosperity. One hundred years later, the Negro is still languished<br>in the corners of American society and finds himself an exile in his own<br>land. And so we’ve come here today to dramatize a shameful condition.</p><h1 id="测试标题3"><a href="#测试标题3" class="headerlink" title="测试标题3"></a>测试标题3</h1><p>In a sense we’ve come to our nation’s capital to cash a check. When the<br>architects of our republic wrote the magnificent words of the Constitution<br>and the Declaration of Independence, they were signing a promissory note to<br>which every American was to fall heir. This note was a promise that all men,<br>yes, black men as well as white men, would be guaranteed the “unalienable<br>Rights” of “Life, Liberty and the pursuit of Happiness.” It is obvious today<br>that America has defaulted on this promissory note, insofar as her citizens<br>of color are concerned. Instead of honoring this sacred obligation, America<br>has given the Negro people a bad check, a check which has come back marked<br>“insufficient funds.”</p><h1 id="测试标题4"><a href="#测试标题4" class="headerlink" title="测试标题4"></a>测试标题4</h1><p>In a sense we’ve come to our nation’s capital to cash a check. When the<br>architects of our republic wrote the magnificent words of the Constitution<br>and the Declaration of Independence, they were signing a promissory note to<br>which every American was to fall heir. This note was a promise that all men,<br>yes, black men as well as white men, would be guaranteed the “unalienable<br>Rights” of “Life, Liberty and the pursuit of Happiness.” It is obvious<br>today that America has defaulted on this promissory note, insofar as her<br>citizens of color are concerned. Instead of honoring this sacred obligation,<br>America has given the Negro people a bad check, a check which has come back<br>marked “insufficient funds.”</p><h1 id="测试标题5"><a href="#测试标题5" class="headerlink" title="测试标题5"></a>测试标题5</h1><p>It would be fatal for the nation to overlook the urgency of the moment.<br>This sweltering summer of the Negro’s legitimate discontent will not pass<br>until there is an invigorating autumn of freedom and equality. Nineteen<br>sixty-three is not an end, but a beginning. And those who hope that the<br>Negro needed to blow off steam and will now be content will have a rude<br>awakening if the nation returns to business as usual. And there will be<br>neither rest nor tranquility in America until the Negro is granted his<br>itizenship rights. The whirlwinds of revolt will continue to shake the<br>foundations of our nation until the bright day of justice emerges.</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;前言：本文是一篇测试文章，截取自马丁路德金的《I have a Dream》。
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
    
    </summary>
    
    
      <category term="live" scheme="http://yoursite.com/tags/live/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>青春</title>
    <link href="http://yoursite.com/2019/01/14/second-blog/"/>
    <id>http://yoursite.com/2019/01/14/second-blog/</id>
    <published>2019-01-13T16:00:00.000Z</published>
    <updated>2019-01-20T14:43:52.133Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<pre><code>前言：这是一篇关于青春的散文，在我的高中时代第一次读到这篇文章，它是那么优美和振奋人心，激励了无数人。</code></pre><a id="more"></a><pre><code>作者：塞缪尔.厄尔曼</code></pre><p>人生匆匆，青春不是易逝的一段。青春是一种永恒的心态。满脸红光，嘴唇红润，腿脚<br>灵活，这并不是青春的全部。真正的青春啊，它是一种坚强的意志，是一种想象力的高<br>品位，是感情的充沛饱满，是生命之泉的清澈常新。青春意味着勇敢战胜怯懦，青春意<br>味着进取战胜安逸。年月的轮回就一定导致衰老吗？要知道呵，老态龙钟是因为放弃了<br>对理想的追求。无情岁月的流逝，留下了深深的皱纹，而热忱的丧失，会在深处打下烙<br>印。焦虑、恐惧、自卑，终会使心情沮丧，意志消亡。60也罢，16也罢，每个人的心田<br>都应保持着不泯的意志，去探索新鲜的事物，去追求人生乐趣。我们的心中都应有座无<br>线电台，只要不断地接受来自人类和上帝的美感、希望、勇气和力量，我们就会永葆青<br>春。倘若你收起天线，使自己的心灵蒙上玩世不恭的霜雪和悲观厌世的冰凌，即使你年<br>方20，你已垂垂老矣；倘若你已经80高龄，临于辞世，若竖起天线去收听乐观进取的电<br>波，你仍会青春焕发。</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;前言：这是一篇关于青春的散文，在我的高中时代第一次读到这篇文章，它是那么优美和振奋人心，激励了无数人。
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
    
    </summary>
    
    
      <category term="live" scheme="http://yoursite.com/tags/live/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
